孩子们 希望你们喜欢茄子炖牛肉
Hey, kids, I hope you like, uh... eggplant goulash.
我要走了 爱你哦 爱你哦
Okay, I got to go. I love you. I love you.
爱你哦 跟我来
I love you. Hey, follow me.
卡车那回之后 你去哪我都跟着
After that truck thing, I'll follow you anywhere.
我只想说昨天真的很浪漫
I just wanted to say that yesterday was very romantic.
我很有信心 今晚我回来
And I'm confident I'm gonna be feeling the same way
也有个浪漫的夜晚 勃基先生
when I get home tonight... Mr. Sparky.
这个小名我不敢说 不过今晚我要定了
I'm not sure about the new nickname, but, uh, I am in.
进来
Yeah.
嗨 你在啊
Hey, there you are!
我有个惊喜要给你
I got a surprise for you.
你们有事要忙吗
Oh, are you two in the middle of something?
- 这个... - 没有
- Well... - No, no.
Adam正要送我出门
Adam was just walking me to the door
他可是世上最浪漫的丈夫了
because he's the most romantic husband in the world.
你可能不会信 他给我的惊喜是...
You would not believe what he surprised me with. He...
好了 没时间闲聊了 再见
Okay, no time for small talk. Bye-bye!
- 你在... - 等你等
- What are you...? - Hold on.
等等
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
好的 她刚刚有点意识混乱
Okay, okay, she was confused for a minute,
- 不过现在没事走了 - 喔
- but she's leaving. - Oh.
听着 我要和你谈谈钢人队的比赛
Okay, listen, I got to talk to you about the Steelers game.
我来这里就是为了这个
That's why I'm here!
我先说会好点
Let me do mine first. It's better.
我给咱们订了
I ordered us,
次日达的空运件
via next day air...
你也知道的 我不愿买的...
which you know I hate to pay for...
钢人队1976年的旧球衣
vintage 1976 Steelers jerseys.
算是你请我看比赛的一点小心意
A little thank you for taking me to the game.
我都不知道要说什么了
I don't know what to say.
我说吧 我是个好兄弟
Well, I'll say it. I'm a good guy.
好兄弟
You are.
你也是我的好兄弟
And you're a good guy, too.
也不...
Eh. Not...
不 你请我看比赛意义重大
No, no, no, no, it means a lot.
我们是看着钢人队长大的 这是属于我们的回忆
We grew up watching the Steelers. It's our thing.
是吗
Is it?
真的是
And is it
我们的独家回忆吗
exclusively our thing?
我意思是
I mean, you know,
你大可邀请Andi去 可你最后选了谁呢
you could've easily invited Andi, but who'd you pick?
是我
Me.
我不太喜欢通过身体表达情感
You know, I'm not much for physical displays of affection,
不过我这次豁出去了
but I'm gonna give you one of these.
拍了三下
Wow. Three pats?
比我结婚那天还多了两下
That's two more than my wedding day.
别告诉别人这件事
Don't tell the guys at work about this.
我不想让他们觉得我是娘娘腔
I don't want them to think I'm a sissy.
-  爸 再见 - 爸 再见
- Bye, Dad! - Bye, Dad!
再见
Bye!
你要去哪里 Burns先生
Hmm. Where are you going, Mr. Burns?
今早有个教育讨论会
There's a parent education seminar this morning.
听着 我家里有紧急情况
Oh, well, listen, not only do I have
需要我回家解决
a pressing family situation I need to handle,
再说我不想开讨论会
I don't want to go to that.
你就盯着我看吗
So, what, are you just gonna stare at me?
你觉得这样吓唬得了我吗
You think that's gonna intimidate me?
我们讨论会或见分晓
Well, we'll find out after the seminar.
Adam
Adam! Adam!
我给你留了位置 这里 Adam
I saved you a seat. Right here. Adam.
嗨 Marie
Hey, Marie.
我不知道你听见了没 Lowell可是给你留了位置
I don't know if you heard, but Lowell saved you a seat.
好 谢谢
Yeah. Thanks.
欢迎各位家长
Welcome parents.
今天的主题是如何阻止学校的欺凌行为
Today's topic will be: "How to stop playground bullying."
开会前 我先道个歉
Before we begin, I'd like to apologize
没有给大家提供茶点
for the lack of refreshments.
若有不满 请自行
If you have any complaints, please feel free
向轮值家长Burns先生诉说
to direct them to your room parent, Mr. Burns.
我有个问题
Okay, I got a question.
可以吧
All right?
我们半个小时不喝水
What has happened in society
家长会会出事吗
that we can't go 30 minutes without a water?
我们不需要水
We don't need water.
我们要的是挖条地道 离开这里
What we need is a way to tunnel out of here!
说完了吗 Burns先生
You done, Mr. Burns?
我说完了
Yeah, I've said my piece.
小组进行情景讨论时
So as you continue to workshop scenarios
要是孩子受到欺凌
in your smaller groups, remember the watch word
记得我们的关键步骤
for when your child feels bullied:
"起身 交谈 离开"
"Stand up, Talk, Depart."
STD 性传播疾病
STD
STD.
好吧
All right?
就叫"起身 交谈 离开"吧
Let's just call it "Stand up, Talk, Depart."
没错 欺凌行为是最恶劣的
Yeah, bullying is the worst.
就这两个人
Okay, so now I got two people
我现在是要选谁和我去看比赛
who think they're going to the game with me.
要是他们又碰面了
If they run into each other again, this whole thing
你要完蛋了
is gonna blow up in my face...
说威胁我的话
said that bully to me.
你要带你妻子去看比赛
You know you got to take your wife to the game.
我拿趣多多给孩子当作早餐 连我都这么觉得
I fed my kids Chips Ahoy! for breakfast, and even I know that.
不是 我知道了
No. I know, I know.
我现在就要去做 跟Don说明白
Now I just got to get to work and break it to Don.
问题是我怎么出去呢
Question is: how do I get out of here?
这就难了
This is tough.
我意思是 换做是我 我会问我自己
I mean, if it were me, I would ask myself,
"Adam会怎么办" 可你就是Adam啊
"What would Adam do?" but you're Adam.
连你都不知道
And you don't know.
那可能没人知道了
It might be unknowable.
你们俩个太可爱了
You guys are so cute together.
Marie 你说的这话
Marie, it doesn't sound like you're talking about
不该在会上说吧
what you're supposed to be talking about.
不好意思 Rodriguez女士
Excuse me, Mrs. Rodriguez.
我觉得你在欺负我的好朋友
I think you're bullying my good friend.
我要起身
So I will stand up...
交谈 然后离开
talk... and depart.
没错 我所做的就是STD
That's right... I just gave you an STD.
- Andi -嘿
- Andi. - Hey.
Don
And Don.
真是"惊"喜啊
What a heart-stopping surprise.
你们两个怎么在一块了呢
What are you two unlikely buddies up to?
我们聊天而已
Oh, just gabbing...
说到你到Andi去看钢人队的比赛
about you taking Andi to the Steelers game.
真是个幸运的女子
What a lucky girl.